cancelon.com 2015-06-07

# Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy

By this Privacy Policy We are committed to safeguarding the privacy of the users of Cancelon, on the domain name Cancelon.com (“the Website”) and in any additional domain name decided upon by the sole discretion of Cancelon LTD and its affiliates (“Cancelon”); this policy sets out how we treat your personal information. The use of Paypal through the Website is subject to the Privacy Policy of Paypal and its terms.

1) Providing Information to the Website  
The use of the Website and its services require registration. When you sign up for the Website we will ask you to provide certain identifying information such as name, address, current email address, phone number and more. In order to make a purchase via the Website, you will have to give also your credit card information. Alternatively you will be able to use PayPal. Without providing the information required, you will not be able to use the Website's services.  
You must provide only true, accurate and complete information and you hereby confirm that the information provided by you answers to this description.

The information you provide in your registration will be kept by the administration of the Website. In case of a transaction between two users and in order to change a name on a reservation, Cancelon will share, both with Buyer and Seller, the full name of the other party.  

You are not required to provide us with any information, but incorrect information or failure to provide all required information may prevent you from using the services on the Website, affecting the quality of the services provided to you as well as impair the ability to contact you. If your details have changed, you should update them in the Website.

When you provide personal information of third parties, you acknowledge that you have received their explicit consent to deliver the information to the Website management for the usage of the Website according to this Privacy Policy.

2) What information do we collect?

We collect, store and use the following kinds of our users' personal information:

(a) information relating to any transactions carried out between you and us on or in relation to the Website, including information relating to any purchases you make of our goods or services. 

(c) information that you provide to us for the purpose of registering with us.

(d) information that you provide to us for the purpose of subscribing to our website services, email notifications and/or newsletters.

(e) any other information that you choose to send to us.

(f) other information. different kinds of personal information which may be collected over or in relation to the Website, such as, but not limited to ads you read, pages you viewed, the services that interested you.

By using the Website you allow the management of the Website to collect and to get the assistance of third parties to collect analytic, anonymous, statistical and aggregative data with relation to your usage of the Website, including information that is relevant to your information and your action on the Website.

3) Using you personal information

Your personal information submitted to us via the Website and the information that will be collected about your habits while you use the Website will be used for the purposes specified in this privacy policy and according to the law – and for the following purposes:

We may use your personal information to:

1\. Enable your use of the services available on the Website;

2\. Administer the Website and developing it;

3\. Improve your browsing experience by personalizing the Website;

4\. Supply to you services purchased via the Website;

5\. Improve the services and content that are offered on the Website and cancel or change current services. The information that will be used by the management of the Website for this purpose will be mostly statistical and will not identify you personally.

6\. Allow you to adjust the services in the Website to your preferences.

7\. Send statements and invoices to you, and collect payments from you;

8\. Send you general (non-marketing) commercial communications;

9\. Send you email notifications which you have specifically requested;

10\. Send you newsletters and other marketing communications relating to our business which we think may be of interest to you by post or, where you have specifically agreed to this, by email or similar technology (you can inform us at any time if you no longer require marketing communications);

11\. Provide third parties with statistical information about our users. However, this information will not be used to identify any individual user;

12\. Deal with inquiries and complaints made by or about you relating to the Website;

13\. Contacting you when the management of the Website believes there is a need for that.

14\. For any other reason that is in the Privacy Policy or in the User Agreement of the Website.

We will not, without your express consent, provide your personal information to any third parties for the purpose of direct marketing.

All our Website financial transactions are handled through our payment services provider, PayPal. You can review the PayPal privacy policy at www.paypal.com. We will share information with PayPal only to the extent necessary for the purposes of processing payments you make via our website and dealing with complaints and queries relating to such payments.

4) Cookies

A cookie consists of a piece of text sent by a web server to a web browser, and stored by the browser. The information is then sent back to the server each time the browser requests a page from the server. This enables the web server to identify and track the web browser.

We may use both “session” cookies and “persistent” cookies on the Website. We may use the session cookies to: keep track of you whilst you navigate the Website and whils you are signed in; and We may use the persistent cookies to: enable our website to recognise you when you visit; and 

All cookies may be deleted from your computer when you sign out or after they reached a specified expiry date or when you close your browser. Some of them may remain on your computer until deleted. 

We use Google Analytics to analyse the use of the Website. Google Analytics generates statistical and other information about the Website use by means of cookies, which are stored on users' computers. The information generated relating to the Website is used to create reports about the use of the Website. Google will store this information. Google's privacy policy is available at: http://www.google.com/privacypolicy.html.

Our payment services providers, Paypal, may also send you cookies. Paypal’s privacy policy is available at: https://cms.paypal.com/il/cgi-bin/marketingweb?cmd=_render-content&content_ID=ua/Privacy_full&locale.x=en_US

Most browsers allow you to reject all cookies, whilst some browsers allow you to reject just third party cookies. For example, in Internet Explorer you can refuse all cookies by clicking “Tools”, “Internet Options”, “Privacy”, and selecting “Block all cookies” using the sliding selector. Blocking all cookies will, however, may have a negative impact upon the usability of many websites, including this one.

5) Disclosures

Information about our customers and Website users is an important part of our business and we are not getting it so we can sell it to third parties. We may disclose information about you insofar as reasonably necessary for the purposes as set out in this privacy policy.

In addition, we may disclose your personal information:

(a) to the extent that we are required to do so by law;

(b) in connection with any legal proceedings or prospective legal proceedings;

(c) to apply our [User Agreement](http://www.cancelon.com/page/User-Agreement) and other agreements and in order to establish, exercise or defend our legal rights, our users or others (including providing information to others for the purposes of fraud prevention and reducing credit risk);

(d) In case you will violate the User Agreement of the Website or if you make via the Website or in connection with it, actions predicted by the administration of the Website as the violation of any law or an attempt to do so.

(e) In any event the administration of the Website will think that disclosing your personal information is required to prevent a serious damage to your body, your property of the body and/or property of a third person.

(f) to the purchaser (or prospective purchaser) of any business or asset which we are (or are contemplating) selling; and

(g) to any person who we reasonably believe may apply to a court or other competent authority for disclosure of that personal information where, in our reasonable opinion, such court or authority would be reasonably likely to order disclosure of that personal information.

(h) to affiliated businesses we do not control: we work with hotels, motels, businesses in the lodging industry and different types of tourist businesses. You can tell when a third party is involved in your transaction. This third party will receive your personal information that is relevant to that transaction.

(i) to any of our employees, officers, agents, suppliers or subcontractors

(j) with your consent. Other than as detailed above, we will sent you a notice when information about you might go to third parties, and you will have an opportunity to choose not to share the information.

(k) to third-party service providers: we employ and work with other businesses to perform functions on our behalf. For examples: analyzing data, providing marketing assistance, providing search results and links, processing credit card payments. They have access to personal information needed to perform their functions, but may not use it for other purposes.

(l) to promotional offers: we may send to our users special offers and promotions on behalf of other businesses. In these cases, we will not give those businesses your personal information.

(m) as part of business transfer. As we continue to develop, our business may be sold to another business. In such transactions, users information is normally one of the transferred business assets but remains subject to the promises made in any pre-existing Privacy Policy, unless the user agrees otherwise. If that ever happens, your personal information will be part of the transferred assets.

Except as provided in this privacy policy, we will not provide your information to third parties and we will not sell, rent, share, or otherwise disclose personal identifiable information from our users for commercial purposes in violation of the commitments set forth in our Privacy Policy.

6) International data transfers

Information that we collect may be stored and processed in and transferred all around the world, and in some cases to countries with different protection laws.   
You expressly agree to such transfers of personal information.  
In addition, personal information that you submit for publication on the Website will be published on the Internet and may be available, via the Internet, around the world. We cannot prevent the use or misuse of such information by others.

7) Security of your personal information

We are taking reasonable technical and organizational precautions to secure your information and to prevent the loss, misuse or alteration of your personal information.

Of course, data transmission over the Internet is inherently insecure, and we cannot guarantee the security of data sent over the Internet.

You are responsible for keeping your password and user details confidential. It is extremely important that you protect against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer. Always sign off when finished using our site.

8) Policy amendments

We may update this privacy policy from time-to-time by posting a new version on our website. You should check this page occasionally to ensure you are happy with any changes.

9) Your rights

(a) You may choose not to provide information, even though it might be needed to use the site.

(b) You may instruct us to provide you with any personal information we hold about you. Provision of such information will be in accordance with any law or regulations and may be subject to:  
(a) Payment of a fee; and  
(b) Supply of appropriate evidence of your identity (for this purpose, we will usually accept a photocopy of your passport certified by a notary plus an original copy of a utility bill showing your current address).

(c) You may add or update your information by logging in to your account and selecting your user profile. We will maintain the old information as well as the new one.

(d) If you do not wish to receive emails and/or mail from us, please write us to [Contact US](http://www.cancelon.com/contact)

We may withhold such personal information to the extent permitted by law.

You may instruct us not to process your personal information for marketing purposes by email us at any time. In practice, you will usually either expressly agree in advance to our use of your personal information for marketing purposes, or we will provide you with an opportunity to opt-out of the use of your personal information for marketing purposes.

10) Third party websites

The website contains links to other websites and it may include third party advertising. We are not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of third party websites. In addition, we do not provide your information to these third-party websites.   
These third-party websites and advertisers are working on their behalf. They use different technologies to advertise to you and to measure the effectiveness of their ads and to personalize their content. We don't have access and/or control over it and the third party websites are not covered by this Privacy Policy. Please contact those websites for further any information about their privacy policy. For further information as to how to opt-out of the collection of the Internet Advertising companies, please go to www.networkadvertising.org

11) Are children allowed to use our site?

Children are not allowed to use our Website. If you are under 18, you may use our Website only with the involvement of an adult.

12) Updating information

Please let us know if the personal information that we hold about you needs to be corrected or updated.

13) User Agreement, notices and edits

If you choose to use the Website, your usage and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Private Policy and to our User Agreement, including limitations on damages, resolution of disputes and application of the law of Israel.  
If you have any questions about this privacy policy or our treatment of your personal information, please [contact us](http://www.cancelon.com/contact).  
Our business is dynamic and changes often and our Privacy Policy and the User Agreement will change as well. Please check the Website for updates on our recent changes. However, you should know that we will never apply less protective Privacy Policy. Unless otherwise is mention, our current Privacy Policy applies to all information that we have about you in your account.

14) Contact

If you have any questions about this privacy policy or our treatment of your personal information, please [Contact Us](http://www.cancelon.com/contact).
